Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Everyone, please listen to my prediction.
You'll hit the jackpot again!
I think this number will win.
I won!
His predictions are very accurate.
I will give you 1,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Hey,
His predictions are very accurate.
You will make a lot of money.
Tsune-yan
No matter how many times you try, you always look like a fake customer.
Seriously?
You are like "I got it, I got it, I got it".
What's that?
You're being way too dramatic, aren't you?
A man wearing a raincoat has arrived.
Raincoat?
Please take my place for a little while.
Yeah, I got it! I got it
Stupid detective.
Oh, it's been a while, hasn't it?
Still dressing like a bum as usual,
Huh? You got fired from the police, didn't you?
The only time I'll leave the police force is when I die.
What are you talking about?
Are you looking for someone?
I search what you like,
The only thing I like is women.
Other than that
Apart from women, I like pistols.
Udon?
You are surprisingly smart.
I'm from the civil engineering department of Gakushin University
Don't you know this guy?
It's Mizusawa Tadao from the Oosawa gang, the Yakuza
This guy?
Don't try to fool me.
when are you going to pay the money?
Please give me three more tablets.
I will pay for it along with that.
Damn it.
Pay now.
I will pay for everything together.
You...
Oh blood!
A murderer!
it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter!
Now, today's special match is this!
Is he already dead?
Mizusawa...
About that photo from earlier?
I couldn't hear the sound.
It's silence.
Hey, someone hurry and call the police
Kamoi.
The pistol used to kill him produces neither sound nor flash.
Eh?
The only thing that comes out is blood.
This
Shobu Inu / The Silent Gun (1967)
(Inu/Dog Series #9)
By the way, there was a rumor that Mizusawa from the Taisei Group
was trading in silent, ineffective, and unrelated handguns in Osaka
At first, I was half in doubt, or rather, I thought it was completely nonsense
As expected, victim Mizusawa had this in his possession
Kimura-kun, the reason the Osaka Prefectural Police suspected
Mizusawa was in Tokyo is what?
Because we were informed that he has business dealings with Nakazawa Trading Company in Chuo Ward, Tokyo
In Nakazawa trading....
The victim's pocket had the memo from Nakazawa trading.
Kimura-kun, did you get a hit on that company?
No, Mizusawa went straight to the Boat racing track
from Tokyo Station, so I followed him
Besides Mizusawa, another man
named Kubo has come to Tokyo.
DW Lugar
Waeser B38
Moltgezel X38
Until now, the characteristic of Moltgezel X38 was that it was a gun that made neither sound nor light
According to scientific examination,
The clothing of the victim
There is almost no inflammatory response otherwise
The reason there are no fingerprints left on the surface of the shell casings is that a special chemical has been applied,
and we are currently analyzing it again
What do you think of Dr Tanimura's
findings from the autopsy?
Here it is.
A single bullet that penetrated his heart has several
times the power of a conventional handgun bullet
Yet, it is characterized by a small amount of bleeding,
causing symptoms similar to internal bleeding
It's a terrifying madness
I believe we cannot leave this unattended for even a moment
We must assume that the president has already spread among the national violent organizations
In response to this horrifying series of murders committed with a deadly weapon,
the Metropolitan Police Department has decided to establish an investigation headquarters today
and will begin a thorough inquiry
Please place your bet.
Another one
Ok here we go.
Even.
Please place your bet.
Is there anyone betting on number 3?
Number 1
All set
Here we go
Even, 2
Shit....
Today’s not my day
I find it hard to settle down.
Are you from Kansai?
I was born and raised in Osaka.
Use this if you like.
No,I can't.
It's ok.
I am winning a lot on my own.
Everyone, take your time
It is very rare these days to do something like that.
Please place your bet.
Would anyone like to bet it first?
Hey, mister! Hey!
Mister!
He's dead.
Again,He was killed by a silent pistol.
Kamoi.
Oh,you're really early!
Good morning.
Wait a minute,
Rent?
Don't worry.
No, my wife is being noisy
but I've already found a place to earn.
Really
Wait a minute,
what's wrong with you?
I haven't said anything yet
Who?
I am the neighbor
Oh, you are in the English department at the women's university, right?
I have a favor of you.
Help me
What?
What are you going to do with me?
Wait a minute, this is troubling
I'm still in my pajamas.
Don't worry.
Um, here it is. you need to read this a bit
They’re all in English.
Which?
Here.
Molt Gezeir, completed in February 1945,
Molt Gezeir was a Nazis pistol and was supposed to be a soundless light,
This meaning it doesn't make noise and doesn't emit light
Molt Gezeir means 'murder accomplice.'
Murder accomplice?
Kamoi.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Come in.
Give me 200 yen.
What are you doing?
I found a golden egg
Golden egg?
That's right
I’ve discovered a wonderful new singer, so I’m on my way to pick them up now.
Come in.
This is the person for the meeting
Osaka Prefectural Police, Kimura Junta?
Thank you for your patience.
I am Nakazawa
Thank you for taking the time out of your busy schedule
Have a seat.
Did you come from the Osaka Prefectural Police?
Ah, recently there have been similar products of
our imported toys circulating in the Kansai area
What I inquired about is a murder case
Yesterday, a man named Mizusawa, an executive of a Yakuza group in Osaka, was killed
This note was found in the man's clothing.
Yakuza member
Do you have any idea about the gang member?
As you can see,
I am mainly engaged in the import and export of high-end toys
We have nothing with Yakuza
Why is this memo there?
Everyone who comes for the transaction receives this memo.
I get it.
By the way, when did this company start?
It was around the end of three years ago
I have been working in America for a long time
I started this job as soon as I returned to my country.
I see.
Come in.
There's a call from the
warehouse, President
Shall I transfer it to you?
Well, I'm going over there
so excuse me.
Ah, this is my secretary, Tachikawa
She should know everything about me.
so please feel free to ask
Have a seat.
Excuse me.
It seems that the president has difficulty with his legs
Yes, he sprained his ankle at a golf course about two years ago
He mentioned that it's because of his age.
Oh, I see
Kamoi.
I've brought the golden egg.
Are you talking about this kid,
the golden egg?
That's right, the pure gold egg.
you mentioned is an exaggeration,
what's her name?
Tamako.
If the egg is up, what's her name?
I'm telling you.
I'm Tamako Tamamura.
I see, her name is Tamako so it comes from golden egg.
Yeah.
It seems like a joke, but it looks like a girl log
You know what?
This girl used to work at a diner in front of the cycling track where I used to work.
She doesn't have family, feeling quite lonely
But she has a bright spirit, and that's her pride
I have a letter from Tsune-san.
I flew here from Osaka with great enthusiasm
I will sing with all my might
Therefore, I look forward to your continued support
Oh, by the way, I brought a souvenir
Here it is
This brings back memories of the rock awakening—thank you!
Isn't it nice to see her heartfelt effort?
Really
I will hire her.
Thanks.
Really?
I'm glad.
but judging by the development of your tits
your voice must have developed well too
Yeah.
By the way, how's the transportation pay?
Will he send you?
That kind of thing doesn't really matter
Please listen my singing quickly
I understand,
Will you send her?
How about it?
Who's paying 20 yen?
20 yen?
That's the money for the Station platform ticket
Did you come with Station platform ticket?
I've been stuck in the bathroom from Osaka to Tokyo
Just in the bathroom?
Please keep that passion alive
Stupid detective has arrived
Detective?
That's bad.
What's wrong?
See you.
Hey hey, that girl...
She saw me and ran away
I still don't quite understand it either.
She thought she would get caught riding without a ticket.
Oh, I see,
Riding for free?
It's none of your business.
That falls outside the jurisdiction of the Osaka Prefectural Police.
Oh, I see.
Well then, shall we go?
Wait a minute
what?
I have something I want to ask
I was planning to work hard tonight, but if you ask me
How about spending 10 minutes for 100 yen?
10 minutes for 100 yen?
Yeah, if Kamoi plays the guitar, then sure
One song is at least 35 yen, right?
This is 100 yen for 3 songs, right?
Even if you predict for 10 minutes,you can earn about 100 yen in that time
Shut up.
You scared me.
Do you know about silent pistols?
I know a little about that.
Do you know?
This is it
so I'll take 100 yen
Don't be stingy
this Kamoi-style dictionary is
something the Metropolitan Police doesn't have
1 min
Thanks.
Look at this.
Should I translate this?
In other words,
Just leave it alone.
I won't ask you
Do you even understand foreign words?
Of course.
You're on a different level than me, aren't you?
Seriously, you're just like a clumsy person
2 mins
Welcome.
Where did Tamako go?
I paid for the travel expenses, but she disappeared.
It was just 20 yen,
You shouldn't exaggerate.
But...
But I think it's really cute that she escaped by riding the train for free.
Really, but where did she go?
I am worried about her getting hit on by men in Tokyo.
You're so noisy,aren't you?
Then go look for it
May I?
Go ahead.
Where are you going?
I'll go around.
Who?
Why was I targeted?
That pistol is amazing.
I can neither hear that sound nor see the fire.
Where's Obata?
In back room.
You're late,Funayama
Stop wasting shots
You committed a senseless murder at the boat race track.
Why do you target the Kamoi?
Don't you know, big brother?
That guy Kamoi was at the scene of the Mizusawa murder and was also involved with Kimura, the cop who took out Kubo
Moreover, it seems he was the one who crushed the nightlife in Osaka with a single gun.
That's right.
Both the Tenchi and the Gamou group were definitely taken down by him
I shot Osako because I saw him, and I won't stay silent
I'll definitely kill him.
Did you forget the boss's orders?
I don't mind if the buyer kills him
We must not shoot him with a pistol.
We have a lot of business to do with this pistol from here on out.
If the police were to do this, this business could not operate.
Be careful!
I need to make a little more effort.
I'm horny.
Tsune! What are you doing?
Hey!
It was nice.
What are you doing?
I found a big cockroach
I'll kill it.
You don't have to.
What's the hell?
You know what?
I wonder where Tamako-san has gone.
She has completely disappeared.
I see.
This is caused by poverty in society.
You talk about difficult subjects.
She didn't have any money, so she rode the Shinkansen without paying.
She mistakenly thought the police had come to arrest her.
Even when I carry my guitar and play on the street,
It's still a poor?
That's right.
What's this?
Oh hand gun
Look, it's just unbearable, this texture.
Huh? It's been a while since I shot this.
I really want to see how good your skills are
Tama-chan.
You scared me.
I might get killed!
Where were you going?
Is that male detective not coming anymore?
It's okay if he comes.
Please listen to my singing.
I want to audition, you know?
This is the guitar.
What is an audition?
An audition is a test, right?
Yeah.
I have one suggestion, though
Huh? Shall we go?
Welcome!
I'm sorry, Dad, I'm late.
Where have you been?
I still haven't borrowed the clothes
Hasn't your favorite band started yet?
It is just about to start
You are an older person, yet it is quite rare for someone your age to like young Latin music.
Don't make fun of it
I am not that old yet,
Don't you think so too?
I would like your autograph.
Are you really okay?
Just wait a minute
I bought Jane's record to practice,Jane is my admired batter
I think Jane's position is just perfect
Ms. Jane, you have 5 minutes until your turn, so please hurry up
That's impossible
Her makeup will definitely take at least another 15 minutes
However, the customer is waiting
Isn't it fine to keep them waiting?
That way the store can make more profit, right?
Please do it as soon as possible, anyway
Give me a lipstick.
It's so noisy.
Who?
Jane,
I really admire you.
Thank you! Do you want my signature?
I want you to listen to the song of a girl who is infatuated with you
I don't have time for that, just go away
Huh? If you make such a scary face, it won't be a beautiful face anymore, so please smile.
You're irreplaceable, so stay away
Why are you being so cold again
kicking this man out
Stay away
I'm completely out of my mind now
Get your hands off of me!
I'll call someone!
Don't be loud.
What are you doing! Stop it!
Be quiet!
Sensei.
Let's call the police!
You have to spend about two hours redoing your makeup.
He's crazy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Club Gather presents tonight. A wonderful show performed
by Takashi Furuya & Freshman
Singing passionate singer
Jane Shimura
I am Tamura Tamako.
Nice to meet you.
She's not Jane, right?
That's true. Yes
Yes.
Stop it.
Who are you?
Let me sing.
I want to sing
Please
Let me sing.
Please let her sing.
This is a request from the president.
Thank you very much
A customer is waiting for you.
I see.
Hello, this is Tamako Tamamura.
Thank you in advance
It was quite good
Really.
Thank you for letting me sing.
I'm glad I came all the way from Osaka.
Thank you very much!
It was wonderful!
It's rare for my father to praise this much
Have a seat.
Do you want to become a singer?
Yes,When I hear the rhythm, my body gets excited.
My body is feeling all tingly, and soon I'll be singing
Thank you very much, but there is someone else I should be saying thanks
Where are you,Kamoi?
Please come over here!
I wonder where Kamoi-san has gone
Mr. Kamoi!
I'm here.
Let me introduce everyone
This is Mr. Daisuke Kamoi
He promoted me.
thank you for taking care of things!
Nice to meet you
I'm Nakazawa, nice to meet you too.
Please have a seat
Thank you very much.
You did well.
I see
This is my daughter Ritsuko.
It's an honor to meet you.
You are in adult mode 100%
My secretary, Tachikawa-kun, is also here
She's a beautiful like Cleo Butler
What a fortunate night this is!
President, you have a phone call
Well then, excuse me
Is he the owner of this club?
He is the president of Nakazawa Trading Company, which manages this club
Wow, he is an incredibly important person, isn't he?
Please
Thanks.
Hello, this is Nakazawa
I get it.
Well then, I'm going home right away
I'm really serious about this
The Shinkansen is fast, I tell you
It took 3 hours and 10 minutes from Osaka to Tokyo
During that time, just sitting on the toilet,
anyone would get numb, right?
Stop saying it.
But I have to bow my head to that passion
Oh, I apologize
What do you think?
I want to hear more of Tamako's song
Would you like to come home with me?
I want to talk while having a meal
I'm really hungry.
You have to behave elegantly.
Be careful with your choice of words.
I'm a little hungry now
You are stupid.
I see, I see.
but you must have been surprised, right?
Even though it's for the passion of Tamako
I feel like I did something a bit wrong in the end
It's okay, Kamoi-san
I will let everyone know.
I'm counting on you,
I'm already dreaming, aren't I?
It's not a dream.
My father is really enthusiastic about it
He says he wants to get a wonderful band for Tamako
Is that a band exclusively for me?
Yes
How about joining our band starting tomorrow?
Hey, Kamoi! Come here for a second!
What?
You know what?
She said....
Stop! Stop it!
That kid is quick on their feet
Here it is.
He fired a pistol from here.
If he had a little better skills, I would be going to hell, no, heaven right now.
It's fine now
Call the police, call the police.
Did I keep you waiting for a while?
No, more than that,
I suddenly called you, wasn't it a bother?
No way.
If you wanted to consult with me
I can fly over immediately
So what is this consultation about?
I wonder if the gun last night
was really aimed at Kamoi-san
Why would someone target you?
I believe it was someone who resents my father who shot
Is there something about Mr. Nakazawa that makes people resent him?
I don't really understand it either
My father came back from abroad at the end of last year
It's his first return in 15 years
My uncle, who had been taking care of me, passed away, and the company needed a successor
So I was really happy that my father came back
But lately, I've been feeling somewhat worried about it.
My father often has nightmares at night or suddenly looks deep in thought with a scary expression
It seems like he is always afraid of something
Kamoi, I'm begging you
Could you please protect my father?
Protect him?
I have a feeling that something very bad is going to happen to my father soon.
Oh, I think that's just your over thinking.
But why are you telling me to be his bodyguard?
Your gun handling last night was truly impressive.
I was amazed.
Oh my god.
That's my weak point.
Anyway, How about seeing stupid detective?
Stupid detective?
She said that her father was being targeted
Can't you figure out who the culprit is?
She's so scared that she can't even sleep at night.
You want me to identify it from the shell casings without fingerprints?
Hey, that's the police work, right?
If there are no fingerprints, they can't identify the culprit
That kind of police is not good,
but regarding Mr. Nakazawa,
You mentioned that he returned to Japan suddenly
was there any reason for that?
I heard that the reason was that he had a traffic accident in America and injured his leg.
In America?
That's about the injury before returning Japan, right?
Yes, that's right.
I see.
Why are you sulking and mumbling like that?
You came to Tokyo after all.
You shouldn't get the wrong idea.
It's really about Ritsuko's biological father
Biological?
Of course
It makes no difference whether his leg injury was caused by a traffic accident or a gunshot.
Kamoi.
What did you just say?
You suddenly changed your tone.
You said he got shot.
That's right.
What's wrong?
You're smart, aren't you?
Of course, I am
You're from the civil engineering department of Gakushin University, right?
That's right.
Excuse me, miss
You mentioned that your father injured his leg while he was in America
Yes
Are you sure?
Of course
When I asked his secretary, Yumiko Tachikawa, the other day, she said it was an injury after returning to Japan
By the time he arrived at Haneda, he was already limping
Please call in the Osaka Prefectural Police forensics team.
I an Kimura by the first investigation division
There was a man named Suginami who was arrested by Smuggling, right?
It was ten years ago?
During the summer.
Do you have his representative for his crimes?
First, he was hospitalized in a different province,
Then he escaped.
That's right.
That was when I had just become a detective.
I was still very much a newcomer.
Suspect Suginami is he
The left rage of a woman wearing a skirt is nearby
Wearing a white hat and sunglasses
Suginami.
I am arresting you on suspicion of drug smuggling.
Stay down.
I won't get caught by the police.
What? The man named Suginami isn't on the list?
Kamoi-san, the detective from earlier....
Ah, Stupid detective.
Why is he so interested in my father?
Don't worry
He's just very business-minded and thinks everyone he sees is a thief
He has a bad habit
I'm not asking him for anything anymore
I was disappointed in him.
You can leave everything to me from now on
I'll completely take away the source of your concerns.
Seriously?
I have never told a lie in my life.
I swear.
I wonder what Kamoi-san's gun handling skills are like
It's such a shame
I wish I could have a pistol here now.
For example
well, this is how it is
Hey, next time, I definitely
want to see it once.
I will use this matchstick.
Another one
Watch out!
President...your daughter...
What's wrong?
On our way back from the police station, when we entered a café together, a bullet came flying in
He's targeting me.
I was targeted with a pistol yesterday, too.
That is a misunderstanding on your part.
What benefit do those guys get?
Come on, let's cheer up a bit
But it's no wonder that Ritsuko is scared, right, Kamoi?
What on earth does this mean?
What exactly is the purpose of targeting us
I wonder, President?
I was asked by the young lady to be a bodyguard
What do you think?
I can also act as your bodyguard.
Hmm, what are you thinking again?
Mr. Kamoi, can't you consider something like this?
The fact that Ritsuko is being targeted is
because she is with you
Speaking of which, it always happens when she's with Mr. Kamoi
No, I just thought that for a moment
Please don't take it the wrong way
Let's discuss the security guard with Ritsuko again and get in touch
Tachikawa-kun, can you ask for and Kamoi's address
Yes, go ahead
But President....
Thank you for everything today.
Take care, young lady
Thank you very much.
There's no need to be scared, Ritsuko.
I was thinking that I would ask someday,
but didn't something happen abroad that made you resentful?
There's nothing like that at all
I've lived boldly without earning any resentment
There's no need to worry
It's room 205 at Happiness Apartment, number 16, right?
My phone number is 4091238, You can get in touch with me right away by asking the building manager.
Please contact me about that.
I'd be able to act as your bodyguard too.
You ask all sorts of people about becoming a security guard, don't you?
That is because I am a security guard by nature.
Well then
Kamoi-san, how about we go to play Clay pigeon shooting together next time?
Clay?  Clay pigeon shooting?
I would really like to go to that.
Is Mr. Kamoi absent?
Are you here?
He's not here.
It's only increased by 1 centimeter so far
1.2.3.4
I am very excited.
When the light is turned on, Kamoi will die.
Kamoi, this is a bit troubling
It's been building up for three months now
What?
It's the rent.
Three months? Really?
Well, that's not good.
Kamoi-san! I won't fall for that today
Excuse me
Come in.
Kamoi-san, oh, he's not here
It's so dark.
He's not here.
I wanted to ask you something
Come in.
I'll turn on the lights
just wait a moment, in that bright place
It's a bit difficult to say
Actually, Aoyama-san....
What’s with that weird voice?
This is Yokotani Tsunekichi, you know
I've wanted you all along.
What?
I loved you
Get your hands off of me!
I know that our social standings are different.
Turn on the lights quickly.
I will shout to call for help.
But
Turn on the lights quickly.
Is this ok?
What's wrong?
It hurts me.
What on earth is going on?
Kamoi.
Tsune-yan
You have a bad habit of seducing women.
I got shot!
Please call an ambulance.
I am going to treat you, so let go of my hand.
He was targeting me.
Does it hurt?
It hurts me.
Just hold on until the ambulance arrives!
Hang in there!
You must not go alone.
It hurts me.
It hurts!
This angle?
Club Gaza?
That's the place where Tamako was singing.
Welcome.
I'll take the cheapest one with weak alcohol
I get it.
Kamoi-san.
We meet quite often, don't we?
That's true, but please have a seat.
I have a little errand to run
Please take your time.
Please.
I find her cool demeanor very attractive.
Kamoi....
I remember this.
it's a scratch from playing,
This is the scar I left on you.
Did you shoot Tsune with this pistol?
I don't know.
Who's your boss?
There's no boss.
Where did you get this?
Hold on.
I have something to talk about
This is the one, after all.
Kamoi-san, please listen to me
Team up with me, let's make some profit together
By the way, what's your name?
I'm Obata
Where can you get this?
We know, let's go together
I can't.
I don't know what you did at the Boat racing track.
I don't know why you're targeting me
I've got this pistol, so I don't need you anymore.
Kamoi, you are something with the police?
Don't say bullshit.
I am not a police dog.
I just like pistols.
I don't make money or kill people
Kamoi, team up with me!
I'll remember this!
Instead, If you betray me, I will crush you.
Okay?
Ah, Kamoi-san!
Obada
Funayama-san
You are the best as a hit man.
Were you watching?
Why didn't you help me?
I let the Kamoi escape and had the pistol taken away
That's impressive, come here
Funayama-san
Come on
We're going to the warehouse.
Oh you are here.
You should at least lock the door
It's careless
If it were a thief, they would take something.
You're the only one who wouldn't do anything
By the way, it seems like you're going in and
out of Nakazawa Trading Company quite nicely
Ah, that's it
Someone named Tamako-san has come from Osaka.
So, I've been taken care of
However, the Victim at the boat racing track had a memo from Nakazawa Trading Company
You were targeted in the Nakazawa garden.
What do you think?
That's your business, right?
Come on, don't say that.
Let's think about it together.
Well, I won't become a dog of police.
Yeah, where are you going leaving
Tsunekichi behind?
It's none of your business.
Were you looking for that pistol?
Hey, don't let the mummy hunter become a mummy himself
You might think I'm such a fool?
But you're not just relaxing here
To be honest,
You know that was aimed at you, and that Tsunekichi is a someone to take your place
I am aware of that.
Well, if that's the case, that's fine,
but you don't know the guy who targeting you, right?
I know,
He's Obata.
but who is the guy?
I don't know.
But still...
But still?
It's none of your business.
Anyway, you should search for Obata
I don't have time to be doing that over here.
Hey, why are you still so busy?
Are you going out to chase women again?
No.
I am going to go shooting with President Nakazawa, I need to get ready
With President Nakazawa, clay shooting?
Are you jealous?
Kamoi.
Can you get me one of President Nakazawa's cigarette butts?
Cigarette butts?
Stupid detective.
When it comes to clay shooting, it's a game for gentlemen, right?
I know.
It's an expensive and luxurious pastime
Can you defy a gentleman?
I can't.
But it seems a bit strange
This one is just too stiff
There's a difference in the feel of steel and the water
Pistol?
No.
You want the cigarette butt he smoked, don't you?
Also, please ask the young lady about her blood type
For what?
Anything is fine
You're really annoying.
Is there something suspicious about President Nakazawa?
That's the secret of the investigation.
I see.
Then I also.....
You're really annoying.
You are really....
Someone who finds everything a hassle.
Why do I have to take responsibility alone?
Why did you try to team up with Kamoi?
Just for business.
Don't you lie.
You tried to betray us by revealing the secret to Kamoi, the one you called the real deal
You're trying to monopolize the new type of pistol all by yourself
If you team up with me to take out the boss,
there's a long way ahead
How about you make up your mind,
Bros!
Shut up!
Turn that way...
You bastard!
Boss?
Take him way soon
You're so great.
Try this.
Thank you very much.
Using a large hunting gun is a good idea, too.
It's truly magnificent
It's a shame that I can't use unconventional shooting styles in clay pigeon shooting.
unconventional shooting styles?
Never mind
Nakagawa-san.
Excuse me for a moment
It's your turn, young lady
I wonder if it will go well.
See you again.
Thank you for your work.
Nozaki-san, please determine the blood type from this cigarette butt.
Yes
Kimura-san
Is it about the blood type of Nakazawa's deceased wife that
I received a request for over the phone earlier?
Did you find anything?
According to the hospital records, it was Blood O type.
Blood O type?
Thank you very much.
Yes, this is Kimura from the investigation headquarters
The result of the analysis is type B
Type B? Thank you very much.
The young lady's blood type is A
Ritsuko is type A, then you might be bad type.
This is common knowledge.
If the mother is type O and the father is type B,
then a child with type A cannot be born
Nakazawa is not Ritsuko's real father
And about that leg injury...
Please don't worry.
Please
About my father too
I know
Kamoi-san
Take it
What is this?
This is a token of my appreciation for you.
Don't mention it
Don't worry,
I hope you like this
See you then.
Young lady?
Thank you very much.
Come in.
Did you call for me?
Please feed the piranhas.
It seems that it's time.
How is your injury?
Not bad
Not bad?
Well, since I was hospitalized after injuring my arm,
I have to stay until I recover
That's right.
Hospitals are places where wealthy people are found.
I can't stand.
Yes,you are right.
What's that?
The young lady gave me this.
Who's the young lady?
From Ritsuko.
Oh wow, that's nice.
Hey, that's nice
Look at this.
That's not good.
I don't like the way you said that.
I got injured because of you.
So what?
What would you do if I lost the use of my arm?
What exactly are you trying to say?
Don’t do that.
Thank you, thank you
Finally, I can stick to dinner with this
What are you doing?
Are you drunk?
You'll catch a cold if you go to sleep.
You look pale.
Blood!
A fire might have broken out.
Fire?
Oh Stupid detective,
what are you doing!
Blood!
Stupid detective.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Call an ambulance
Call an ambulance?
Where did the fire break out?
Where?
Stupid detective.
You can't die!
Shut up.
Can you be a little quieter?
You act superior.,
If this guy dies,I am angry with you guys.
Does he need a blood transfusion?
Using my blood
I'll do anything!
But that can wait until we go to the hospital
This ambulance is slow. Hey, Drive faster.
Stop it!
Don’t do that.
Drive faster.
Don't push it too hard,
If you do that, we will take you out of the ambulance.
Stupid detective.
Have you regained consciousness?
Don’t do that.
Shut up.
Nakazawa...
What's wrong with him?
Stupid detective.
Hurry up.
I thought I could calm down a bit more,
but it’s only been three years
I'll say goodbye to Japan again
Don’t complain
I am not complaining.
Have you forgotten how I picked you up from being a beggar while touring in America?
Stop bringing up the past
I should have done enough too
During the day I'm a secretary, at night I'm your mistress
But I'm already worn out.
There are also good days
What happened?
Has something happened?
What does this mean?
You'll understand soon enough
Father, it's something that you can't tell me?
Oh, President
How did it go?
We killed the detective.
He dead?
He can't survive.
Yumiko, hurry!
After that, If you kill Kamoi, everything will be fine.
Kamoi-san... Father... Please don't kill him
Shut up!
Don't say unnecessary things!
Father...
Yes, this is the investigation headquarters
What!? Kimura-kun was shot!?
Stupid detective, it's my blood!
This is Daisuke Kamoi's blood
If it's not enough,
I will give you as much as you want.
Stupid detective.
I would be very lonely if you were gone.
Don't die
You can't die
The crime scene, at the Sakuraoka
Happiness Apartment in Shibuya,
Weapon was Molto
Gazelle X38,
We are launching an investigation.
Yes.
Stay strong.
Doctor, please save him, okay?
I understand, I understand
You understand, right?
This is a lifelong request I have for you.
Nurse.
Let me ask you for one too
Stupid detective.
Have you regained consciousness?
You.
What did you just say?
Huh? What's wrong, Nakazawa?
Nakazawa is...
a fake!
What do you mean?
Is that really true?
He killed Ritsuko's father in America
He swapped places with him.
I see...
He tried to kill me because I found out about it.
The truth is, he's a notorious criminal named Suginami
Suginami? Is that how it was?
Yeah....
Let the investigation headquarters know
I understand, I understand. Don’t worry.
More importantly, you need to get better
Okay?
Now, please come out.
Stupid detective.
I will avenge you.
I will definitely do that.
Kamoi-san
What's wrong?
Nakazawa and the others have fled.
They put me through a terrible ordeal.
Where on earth did they go?
I don't know
Please protect me and let me escape
I'm scared...I'm scared...
But now that I've come,
it's okay. Don't worry
Kamoi-san.
I knew this would happen.
Guide me to Nagata's place
Hurry up.
It's dangerous to go any faster, so I can't increase my speed.
I'm not talking to you
Hurry up.
Thank you for your patience.
We are ready,
so please prepare for the transaction
1 pistol 100,000 yen
What?
Please prepare 300,000 yen for one case
This differs from what we agreed upon.
This shouldn't be expensive
We put a great deal of effort into making this malt gazelle
Our boss is waiting.
Don't move!
Damn it.
Turn off the lights.
It's me.
where's the president?
Who's here?
Kamoi
He's alone?
Yes.
Don't let him get away!
kamoi is alone here.
This isn't good.
I can't see the fire,
I can't see where the enemy is.
Ritsuko.
Kamoi-san.
I feel scared.
Kamoi is with Ritsuko.
Surround them.
If we stay here, we'll be killed. we have to run and escape—no matter what.
Miss,  Nakazawa isn't your real father
I thought so
Well, that's because there was a criminal named Suginami
who killed your father in America and He swapped places with your father.
Upon learning that the police knew about it, he tried to kill Stupid detective and tried to escape.
Suginami.
Won't you face me in a contest?
Come on.
Kill two of them.
You have finally revealed your true colors.
Alright.
We can see him.
Go!
Young lady! Cross over to that platform!
Over there?
I'll do it first, so watch closely! Got it?
Young lady! Here! Got it?
If you stay here,
you'll be fine
How about you?
This brat.
I'm going to take revenge for Stupid detective.
Then I'm going to show you the pistol technique you said you wanted to see.
Come on, Suginami
I'll beat you!
Don't move,Kamoi.
Kill him!
Hurry up.
Let's get started!
Damn it.
We don't stand a chance of winning.
Let's do this.
Target that trunk.
Steal that trunk
Hurry up.
Damn it.
Take it away!
Hurry up.
Sugiyama, You should turn yourself in.
Shut up!
Our game is over.
You should turn yourself in.
What the heck!
Suginami.
There are only two rounds left in your pistol.
There are plenty of pistol rounds left.
Don't run away!
Ha!
Tsune-yan.
Tama-chan,What's wrong?
I was surprised when I read the newspaper.
I have returned from the tour.
I see, well, come on in and sit down
Um, well, Where's Kamoi-san?
He is out for a bit.
I see, um, How about Ritsuko-san?
She was not prosecuted.
What does that mean?
It means She did not become a criminal.
I see, that's great!
And usually, I think about this on the train when I'm coming back
I'll stop singing songs.
I thought I would become a wife.
You would become a wife?
That's nice.
So, with whom?
Well....
It's a bit embarrassing to say.
I'm embarrassed too.
I will cherish you.
Don't say stupid things.
I am not talking about you.
I am thinking of Kamoi-san.
The police chief?
Superintendent General of the Metropolitan Police Department
You are receiving a gift from a very distinguished person, aren't you?
I can't call you a stupid detective.
Since you’ve been praised in the newspaper, I can’t speak to you roughly like that.
Shall I call Kamoi-san and you now?
Kamoi-san
Kamoi-san?
It's kind of creepy
I feel like wearing a silk hat and tuxedo.
Call me Kamoi.
I see, so I guess I really like to be called stupid detective.
Yeah.
By the way, there's a great udon shop that opened
Is that true?
The udon there costs 30 yen.
That's cheap!
Next time I come to visit,
I'll bring you a souvenir.
Is that so?
Sorry about that, I appreciate it
By the way...
What?
Fee for the trouble of running the errand.
I can offer you a special price—50 yen is fine.
You are a truly awful person.
You would be better off dead.
Young lady.
Hang in there.
THE END